Welcome to my complete guide to angulars, it's great to have you in this course.
You'll learn what an angular is and how you can use it to build great front end web applications
with him.
Highly reactive web application with great user experience to it during this course.
You will learn all of the individual building blocks that make up the corners before us later too
dive into these more advanced features.
And we will build a project throughout the course putting all the things you will learn
in theory where you practice throughout the course into a real project perspective so you can see
how are you going to apply it there.
And it's like you can see how you build real web applications with the things you learn here.
So with that I say let's dive into that and let's dive into the most important question first.
What's an angular?